Rodhi Faisal Mufid

Portfolio Website: https://www.almufid.tech

Founder, Web Developer

SUMMARY

As a programmer specializing in both Back-end and Front-end development, skilled in designing and maintaining responsive systems and applications tailored to client needs. I am deeply committed to staying updated on the latest technological developments and consistently strive for self-improvement and learning. This dedication enables me to contribute optimally to each project.

I hope to make a significant contribution towards achieving the company's goals and utilize technology as the primary driver for business success. I am committed to enhancing the organization's success through my skills and dedication.

EXPERIENCE

Upwork

Freelance Web Developer (Python)

January 2024 - Present

Creating and manage a web / gui app. Tech stack is RestAPI,
Python, Django, HTML, CSS, Bootsrap, JavaScript

Muanamedia Bimbel

Co-Founder

March 2022 - Present

- Creating and manage a company profil website, new event, and program of education
- Creating a content strategy for content planning, and copywriting for content
- Manage Muanamedia team for the success of Muana's program

PT. Stechog Robotika Indonesia

Software Developer Intern

August - December 2022

- Create a portfolio web using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Tailwind
- Create a four operator calculator using JavaScript, Node.js
- Create a UI using Figma and build API using Express, and MySQL
- Directing a frontend team, and dividing tasks for the process of working the project

SMPN 33 Bandar Lampung

Teacher Assistant

August – December 2021

- Provide administration data entry assistance at school
- Directly involved in the implementation of literacy, numeracy, and technology
- Creating a website for classroom learning in English Subject using HTML, CSS
- Teacher assistance in completing administrative, and classroom learning

PROJECTS

Virus Malware Detection App

Developed a Web App and Sistem using Back-end tehnologies is Python, Django, REST API, and Front-end is HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, and with Jupyter for build Machine Learning model

Check my website & github portfolio for other project: github.com/themufid

CONTACT

- · Indonesia (Open to Remote)
- +62 852 6674 5599
- almufid.business@gmail.com
- linkedin.com/in/rodhifaisalmufid
- · github.com/themufid
- Instagram.com/almufid.tech
- · twitter.com/almufid_tech
- zaap.bio/rodhifaisalmufid

CORE SKILLS

Hard Skills:

- · Python, Django, REST API
- · HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- · JavaScript, Vue.js
- · Copywriting, Digital Marketing
- Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, Postqree
- Sosmed Management, Design

Tools:

- · Git/Github
- · Linux OS, VMWare
- · Visual Studio Code
- Jupyter
- · Trello, Canva, Notion
- WordPress
- · Grammarly, Meta Business

EDUCATION

IIB Darmajaya

Informatics Engineering

GPA 3.69 out 4.00

(Mei 2019 - November 2023)

CERTIFICATION

Udemy, Inc: The Complete
Web Development

Bootcamp

BWA: Bootcamp Front-end
Developer: Mastering Vue.js 3

ID-Networkers:
Linux Cerification

 STMI: Certified School of Website (C.SW)

Other Certifications:

https://www.linkedin.com/ in/rodhifaisalmufid

HOBBIES

- Reading
- Writing
- Traveling